Hilda Mason, City Council 029
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - FY 88 Budget: UDC February 20 1988 Public Hearing (extra copies testimony/staff notes) 1 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - FY 88 Budget: UDC February 20 1988 Public Hearing (extra copies testimony/staff notes) 2 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - FY 88 Budget: UDC February 20 1988 Public Hearing (extra copies testimony/staff notes) 3 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - FY 88 Budget: UDC February 20 1988 Public Hearing (extra copies testimony/staff notes) 4 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - FY 87 Supp. Ed. Ctte Report 6/12/87 Mark up, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - FY 87 Supp. Bd. Of Ed. Questions/Answers/Legls, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - FY 87 Supp. - UDC Questions/Answers/Legls, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - FY 87 Ed. Comm Testimony, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - H.R 4776, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Performance Measures Review, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Second Supplemental Budget for FY 1988 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - 1988 Budget Info 1 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - 1988 Budget Info 2 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - 1988 Budget Info 3 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - 1988 Budget Info 4 of 4, 1987-1988 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - FY 1987 Supplemental- General Materials (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Budget Hearing Friday 2/20/1987 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Mayor, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Responses to Questions Submitted with February 16 1988 Letter about UDC Budget (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - UDC FY 89/Revised 88' Budget Hearing, 1988 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - UDC FY '89 Revised '88 Budget Hearing: 22 February 1988 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees of DCPL FY 1987 Suppl. Budget Request (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Committee of the Whole - Dennis Desmond, 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Budget Hrg. 1/25/87, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Meeting Feb. 25 1987 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - FY 87' Budget: CTEE on Education Report, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Special CTTE Mtg: FY '87 Supp. Budgets Mark-Up June 12 1987 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - June 8 1987 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - June 8 1987 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - CTTE. Supplemental Hear. 6/1/87, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - FY 87 Budget: Gramm Rubman Issues, undated (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - FY 87: Budget: Education as a priority in D.C, undated (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - FY 87 Budget: Correspondence Re UDC /Board of Budget Form Governmental Sources, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - FY 87 Budget: Correspondence (Public) Re UDC/Board Budget, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - FY 87 Budget: DCPS Testimony Part 1, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - DCPS FY 1987 Budget Testimony Pt. II Second day, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - FY 1987 Budget Questions, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - UDC FY 87 Budget Testimony, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries - Regular Meeting 3/23/87 - 4/6/87 - 4/4/87, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Ella Baskin Committee Staff 3/23/87, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - FY 87: Budget Questions and Answers UDC, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - FY 87: Budget Questions and Answers UDC, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - FY 87: Budget Parents United Positions, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - FY 1987 Bd of Ed.Budget Questions and Answers (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Fiscal Year 1986 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - FY '86 Supplemental Budget Request Ed. Ctte Report, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Fiscal Year 1985 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - March 25 1980. (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Fiscal Year 1984 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Preliminary FY '86 Budget Info, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - January 21 1983 Budget Hearing Questions (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - UDC FY '86 - Budget Testimonies, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - FY 1987 Budget = (Library), 1986 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - FY 1986 Budget (Library), 1984-1990 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - FY 1985 Budget ( Library), 1984 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - FY 1984 Budget (Library), 1983 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - D.C Public Library -"Establishment of 1981 Budget" Memorandum (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - FY '83 Reprogramming 5-16, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - FY 83' "Reprogramming5-37", 1983 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Reprogramming 6-1, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Reprogramming 6-3, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Parent Teacher Association (PTA), 1987-1988 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Partnerships in Education, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Parents United for Full Funding, 1988-1990 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Peace Child Foundation, 1983 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - Permanency Planning Task Force, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - Pre Schools (Gen. Issues), 1984 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - Prayer in Schools, 1984-1985 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - Public Education Legal Services Project, 1982 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - Race Relations/Civil Rights/Black Issues, 1982-1983 (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Reading IS Fundamental, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Reorganization Plan- 1988 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - Reprogramming, 1984-1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Residency, 1987-1988 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Retirement, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Salaries and Benefits for Educators, 1983-1987 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - School Lunch - Nutrition, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - School Closings, 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - School/Safety/Security, 1982-1985 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Science and Mathematics Curricula, 1982-1988 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Science and Mathematics, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - School Transit, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Searches in Schools, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - School without Walls, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Constituent Complaint, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Sexuality Programs, 1984-1987 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Sharpe Health School, 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Southeastern University, 1983-1983 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Smart Program, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Special Education, 1972-1985 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - J.C Nalle Elementary School, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Markie Reed Learning Center, undated (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - McKinley School Repairs, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 21)
  - Holy Temple Church/Buchanan School, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 22)
  - Recommended Adjustments in FY '91 Council Budget, 1991 (Box 86, Folder 23)
  - Rvilin Report, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 24)
  - Youth Affairs: Street Academy for Drop outs, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 25)
  - Special Education; Problems 1 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 26)
  - Special Education; Problems 2 of 2, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 27)
  - State Health Plan 81-86, 1981 (Box 86, Folder 28)
  - Standardized/Comprehensive Tests, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 29)
  - Student Health, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 30)
  - Students - Individual Cases, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 31)
  - Street Academy of DC, 1969-1986 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Student Issues General, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 33)
  - Student National Education Association, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 34)
  - 1982-1983 Student Charges at Statue and Land Grant University (Box 86, Folder 35)
  - Student Loan Defaults, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Takoma Elementary Schools, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Taxation and Education, 1981-1983 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Teachers, 1982-1986 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Television, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 40)
  - Study of Teacher Incentives - 6/1989, 1984 (Box 86, Folder 41)
  - Teachers Issues, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 42)
  - Teachers Tests for Certification, 1985-1987 (Box 86, Folder 43)
  - Application for Order to Show Cause and for Adjudication of Contempt, 1978 (Box 86, Folder 44)
  - Notice of Motion Restraining Order, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Fiscal Year 1993 Supplemental Budget and Rescissions of Authority Request Act of 1993 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Bill 10-122; The Fiscal Year 1993 Supplemental Budget and Rescissions of Authority Request Act of 1993 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Bill-10-121 The Fiscal, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Referral of Proposed Legislation, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Act D.C 9-187 April 7 1992 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Transmittal of Enrolled Legislation, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Bill 9-438 "The Fiscal Year 1993 Budget Request Act", 1992 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Bill 9-508, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Bill 9-439 the "Fiscal Year 1992 Supplemental Budget and Rescission of Authority Request Act of 1992 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Budget: Meeting/Bills/Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education Budgets/Teachers/Retirement/Library Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Bill 10-121 the Fiscal Year 1994 Budget Request Act, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - FY 1993 Revised and FY 1994 Operating Budget Requests (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Notice of an Additional Legislative Meeting on March 24 1993 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Bill 9-438, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Test Scores, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Harry Thomas, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Title I, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Teenage Pregnancy - Prevention (Gen. File), 1984-1985 (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Transit (Student) Subsidies Etc., 1978 (Box 87, Folder 21)
  - Tuition, 1982-1985 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Tutorial Programs, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - D.C.P.S Volant-ear - 1988 (Box 87, Folder 24)
  - Values - Centered Goals, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 25)
  - Vocational Education, 1988-1989 (Box 87, Folder 26)
  - James Dent Walker, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 27)
  - Washington Child Development Council, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 28)
  - Washington Lawyers' Committee for Civil Rights under law, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 29)
  - Wash. Parent Group Fund, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Local Universities' Presidents (General Issues), 1985 (Box 87, Folder 31)
  - E.P.T.C, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 32)
  - Equalization Reports (DCPS), 1988 (Box 87, Folder 33)
  - Family Support Act of 1988, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 34)
  - Federal City Council Report - Analysis, 1984-1989 (Box 87, Folder 35)
  - Federal Spending and Policy for Education, 1983 (Box 87, Folder 36)
  - Fillmore Arts Center, 1984-1987 (Box 87, Folder 37)
  - Georgetown/Tutoring Project, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 38)
  - Gifted and Talented Programs, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 39)
  - Health, 1985-1987 (Box 87, Folder 40)
  - Hispanic/Latino Issues, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 41)
  - Initiatives (General), 1985-1988 (Box 87, Folder 42)
  - Labor- Relations (NEA, 1982-1983 (Box 87, Folder 43)
  - Law and Education, 1984-1990 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Leasing Authority of DCPS, 1987-1988 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Board of Educ. - Left Mitch Case, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Calvin Lockbridge, 1988-1989 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Lorton College Program, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Lovejoy School (NAFEO) National Ass. For Equal Op. in Higher Ed., undated (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Mayor's Commission on Post Secondary Education, 1988-1989 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Mayor's Committee on Public Schools, 1981 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Mayor's Public Hearing on Funding for the D.C. Pub. School, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Mayor's Purchasing Directive/Board of Education, 1983 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Medical and Dental Manpower Act of 1970 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Mentor Program, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Merit/Incentive Pay, 1982-1984 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Multicultural Career Intern Program, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - National- Education Association, 1984-1987 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, 1987-1989 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Office of Post Secondary Education 2 of 2, 1990 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - 1993 Miscellaneous Budget (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Interagency Council on Education Summit, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - IAC Standard Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Fiscal Year 1994 Pay Recommendations (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Mason's Staff Committee on Public Services Committee Meeting December 6 1993 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Interagency Committee on Finance Budget 1 of 2, 1988-1995 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Interagency Committee on Finance Budget 2 of 2, 1988-1995 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - IAC Budget Finance Downsizing Back-up/Implementation of Summit Agreement/Closing Medicaid, 1992-1994 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - IAC Budget Finance Committee 1 of 2, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - IAC Budget Finance Committee 2 of 2, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Enrolled Versions (for filing), 1994 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Bill 10-323 "Omnibus Spending Reduction Act of 1993" (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Office of the Secretary 1 of 4, 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Office of the Secretary 2 of 4, 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Office of the Secretary 3 of 4, 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Office of the Secretary 4 of 4, 1993-1994 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - A Proposed Resolution: Natalie C. Greene Appointment Emergency Declaration Resolution, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Howard U UDC Miner Building, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Bill 9-48 UDC Compensation Agreement Act of 1991 Report Enrolled Legislation Correspondence (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - UDC Satellite Campus, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Board of Governors of DC Law School Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Office of the Secretary Committee Report, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - DC Library Trustees, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Office of the Secretary 1 of 2, 1994-1996 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Office of the Secretary 2 of 2, 1994-1996 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - Education in Partnership with Technology Corporation 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - Education in Partnership with Technology Corporation 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Friday July 1988, 1998 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - 6/13/88 Committee Meeting 6. -253 - ph 6. 7-443, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - 1/14/88 Budget Hearing DCPS, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - Ed. CTTE Regular Mtg. May 11 1987 Interim Bd. Of Law School 1 of 2 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Ed. CTTE Regular Mtg. May 11 1987 Interim Bd. Of Law School 2 of 2 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - Education CTTE. Mtg. 4/14/87 Joint Roundtable - Gov't Op PR 7-77/PR 7-72/Bills 7-160/7-161/7-162, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Ed. Ctte. Reg. Meeting - 7/11/86 UDC Management Plan Briefing (Rescheduled), 1986 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Ed. Ctte. Pub. Roundtable. On Bill 6-472 June 23 1986 - 2:30 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Ed. Ctte. Regular Meeting (3/24/86) Briefing: Use and Leasing Authority of the Board of Education, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Ed. Ctte. Reg. Meeting (Nov. 24 1986) UDC Briefing on Updating of Mgmt. Plan 2:00 - Room 114 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Committee on Education - Briefing on DCPS Proposed Contract Authority March 10 1986 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - CTTE: on Education - Mon. Jan. 13 1986 Approval of PR 6-165 and PR- 6-166 (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - Committee on Education Feb. 10 1986 Briefing on a New Student (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Ctte. On Education - Reg. Meeting Jan. 27 1986 - Cancelled (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Education - Dec. 16 1985 Future of UDC Roundtable (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Education Ctte. Mtg 3/23/87 Mark-up PR 7-31 UDC: Reynolds, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - Ctte. On Ed. - March 9 1987 PR 7-31 Arthur Reynolds Confirmation Resolution (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Committee on Ed. - Additional Mtg. 2/27/87 Approval of Comments on PR 7-39, 1987 (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Committee on Education - Regular Mtg. Feb. 9 1987 - Libraries (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Ctte. On Education Regular Mtg. Fri. Jan. 30 1982 :2pm UDC Engineering (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Ctte. On Education - Special Meeting December 15 1986 - UDC Report (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Ed. Ctte. Meeting (Special) 10/3/86 Mark-Up of PR 6-45 and PR 6-456, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Ed. Ctte. Roundtable on Bill 6-328 Oct. 27 1986 2:00pm - Chamber (Teachers' Retmt. Standards Act of '85', 1985 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Ed. Ctte./Human Serv. Ctte. Meeting Briefing on Spec. Edu for Juv. Deliq 12/9/85 - 2:00 pm - Rm. 114, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education - Meeting Nov. 15, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education - Oct. 28 1985 Discussion of - PR 6-57 (Ft. Lincoln) (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - UDC Continuation Hearing 10/10/85 Opening Statement/questions/agenda, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Education - 13th Meeting October 16 1985 PR 6-223/224/225/219/221 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Opening Statement/Questions UDC Hearing 9/23/85, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Ed. Ctte. Public Hearing (Cont.) UDC Sept. 23 1985 - 2:00PM Room 224 3rd Hearing (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Ed. Ctte. Special Meeting to Approve Comments on PR 6-200 and PR 6-206 (9/20/85), 1985 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Ed. Ctte. Public Hearing (Cont..) on UDC Sept. 19,1985 - 4:00PM - Chamber 2nd Hearing (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - A Proposed Resolution: Natalie C. Greene Appointment Emergency Declaration Resolution, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Howard U UDC Miner Building, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Bill 9-48 UDC Compensation Agreement Act of 1991 Report Enrolled Legislation Correspondence (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - UDC Satellite Campus, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Board of Governors of DC Law School Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Office of the Secretary Committee Report, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - DC Library Trustees, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Office of the Secretary 1 of 2, 1994-1996 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Office of the Secretary 2 of 2, 1994-1996 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Education in Partnership with Technology Corporation 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Education in Partnership with Technology Corporation 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - 6/13/88 Committee Meeting 6. -253 - ph 6. 7-443, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - 1/14/88 Budget Hearing DCPS, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Ed. CTTE Regular Mtg. May 11 1987 Interim Bd. Of Law School 1 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Ed. CTTE Regular Mtg. May 11 1987 Interim Bd. Of Law School 2 of 2 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Education CTTE. Mtg. 4/14/87 Joint Roundtable - Gov't Op PR 7-77/PR 7-72/Bills 7-160/7-161/7-162, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Ed. Ctte. Reg. Meeting - 7/11/86 UDC Management Plan Briefing (Rescheduled), 1986 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Ed. Ctte. Pub. Roundtable. On Bill 6-472 June 23 1986 - 2:30 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Ed. Ctte. Public Hearing on UDC - BOTS Nominations - Sept. 19 1985 - 2PM (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Ed. Ctte. 12th Meeting Comments on Bill 6-135 - Sept. 9 1985 1pm - Rm 115 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Ed. Ctte. Public Hearing - UDC Expendts. Sept. 9 1985 - 2:00 PM - Chamber 1st Hearing (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education 10th Meeting CIP Briefing - June 24 1985 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - DCPS FY' Supplemental. Budget Request. (Background Info. etc.) 5/31/85, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Supplemental Budget Issues Council Period VI, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Ed. Ctte. Mark-Up Mark-up Meeting 5/31/85 FY '85 Supplemental. Request. Bd. Of Educ., 1985 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Ed. Ctte. Pub. Hearing - May 24 1985 FY ' 85 Supplemental Budget Request (DCPS) (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Ctte. On Education - 8th Reg. Meeting May 13 1985 - UDC Briefing (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - Ctte. On Education 7th Reg. Meeting April 22 1985 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Ctte. On Education 6th Reg. Meeting March 25 1985 ----- 2 pm (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Ctte. On Education 5th Reg. Meeting March 11 1985 Cancelled (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Ed. Ctte. 3rd Regular Meeting Feb. 11 1985 - Cancelled (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Ctte. On Education 2nd Reg. Meeting Monday, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Ctte. On Educ. Meeting - 1st January 14 1985-2pm (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Education - Meeting December 10 1984 2:00pm UDC Self- Study Briefing (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - UDC Self Study - Ed. Ctte Briefing, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Education - Meeting - December 10 1984 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Education - November 29 1984 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Ctte. On Ed. Meeting - Additional. 11/29/84 UDC Salary Bonus, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Education Committee Meeting - Briefing on UDC Salary Bonus - PR 5-1031/11/26/84 2PM, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Ed. Ctte. /Jud Ctte. Briefing Security in DCPS: 10/31/84, 1984 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Committee on Education and Committee on the Judiciary Joint Briefing October 31 1984 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Committee on Education and Committee on the Judiciary - Joint Briefing October 31 1984 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Ctte. On Educ. 22nd Regular Meeting Bill 5-516 Oct. 22 1984 - 2PM (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Committee on Education October 22 1984 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education - Meeting October 9 1984 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearing - Bill 5-493 "Asbestos Abatement Act of 1984 October 5 1984 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Ctte. On Education 1st Reg. Meeting Jan. 14 1985 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education - Sept. 24 1984 Briefing on Asbestos (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Ctte. On Education -21st Reg. Meet 9/24/84: Asbestos Briefing II, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education - 20th Regular Meeting: July 9 1984 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Ed. Reg Mtg. July 9 1984 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Educ. Meeting FY 1984 Sup. Budget Mark-up 6/25/84 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Education - 6/11/84 18th Regular Meeting: UDC Ts and CIP, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Education: 5-29-84 Regular Meeting (Roundtable), 1984 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - The District of Columbia School Age Care Community 1 of 2, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - The District of Columbia School Age Care Community 2 of 2, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Education: 5-14-84 Regular Meeting (cancelled), 1984 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education 16th Regular Meeting -- 4/9/84, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Ed. FY 1985 Budget Hearing, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Education FY: '85 Budget Hearing -Feb. 14 1984 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Clarence Daniels Budget Hearing -UDC February 17 1984 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Ed. FY 1985 Budget Hearing February 14 1984 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Education: 2/24/84 FY' 85 Budget Mark up Meeting, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Education: Meeting - 2/27/84: Regular Meeting, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Education Regular M'TG Feb. 13 1984 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Educ. Committee Meeting 14th Regular 1/30/84 Rescheduled, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Let's Talk about Education Improvement, 1996 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Legislative Drafting Manual, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Education in Partnership with Technology, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Texas Academic Skills Program, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - 1997 District of Columbia Directory for District of Columbia a City Council (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Teachings next Generation, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Conflict Resolution Education, 1996 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - School Closing Recommendations- 1996 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - DC FY 1996 Summary of Authorized and Proposed Positions Embracing and Empowering our Youth (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York Grants and Appropriations - 1990 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - The Maryland One-Day Trip Book, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Financial Responsibility and Management Assistance Authority, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Press Release from Authority on the State Functions Report, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - DC FY 1998- FY 2003 Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - DC FY 1998- FY 2003 Capital Improvement Plan and FY 1998 Capital Budget Department of Public Works Transportation Program (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - DC FY 1998 Budget and Financial Plan Executive Summary, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - DCHA Directory, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Testimony FY 1998 Budget and FY Impact Settlement, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Board of Education FY 1997 Recommended Budget Request, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - FY 1997 Capital Improvement Budget DC Schools, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - DC Procurement Practices Act of 1985 Amendment Act of 1990 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Washington D.C Residents Study June 1997 (Box 96, Folder 4)